um
wow
we really did it so this is what a
lenium looks like
we finally did it good work everyone
daddy
were you in the lab all night again
anna we succeeded in extracting allenium
you really did that's so great daddy
but you should look after your health
too
daddy i prepared you some breakfast so
i'll be right over
who are you
what do you want
nobody could have survived that
explosion
mini force
new heroes rise
i called for this elder's meeting today
because the lizard army has taken the
illinium that we extracted after a long
research
the lizard army already has the
amplifying prism
if they also get the controlling cube it
will be a disaster not only for the
animals but also for the human world
if we don't get the illinium back from
this evil force quickly enough the whole
earth will be in danger
who knew the lizard army would be so
powerful
what's the plan commander chen
to fight the strong lizard army i plan
to form a special task force with the
best rangers
without getting noticed by the enemy
this team of elite rangers must quickly
recover the illinium
these rangers all graduated from
training school top of their class they
are serving in various areas
this is ranger bolt he has super speed
ranger sammy has super jumping skills
ranger lucy has super defense skills
and ranger max is super powerful
the illinium must be reclaimed very
swiftly and very safely
and these ranges are the best option for
the mission
i ask that you authorize the task force
and the mission
i don't think we have any other option i
vote sending the rangers
that's right
we have to take action fast
all right
we'll make the decision right here and
now
commander chen
headquarters gives you full support
bring back the illinium
good it will be done
commander chen
one moment please anna
why are you
please take me with you i want to
volunteer for this mission
i'm sorry i can't allow that
commander
nobody knows olyny more than i do
even so
this mission is too dangerous
i'm qualified because i've watched my
father's research for years you'll
definitely need my help
hmm
all right
you're going with him
thank you commander
when i get to the last one
the real power of a lithium will finally
work
yes you're amazing sue sir
tacos
now we're only missing the controlling
cube how is the search going
great
i have already discovered where it is
good
when i have the cube
i will rule over every animal and even
over the
this humans so nice
being assigned for the past two years in
a town without any crimes i'm such a
lucky guy
i could just live in this peaceful place
forever
ah
oh commander chad
what brings you to this rural town
ranger vote i have an order from head
office the enemy took an important
matter developed in the headquarters lab
we are forming a special task force in
order to bring it back
you are being assigned to the task force
and must report back to headquarters now
i still have time left in this town
order from headquarters get ready right
away ah but i don't want to go i like
this post i want to finish my assignment
in this town this is no time for such
behavior
come on commander no please let me stay
here
you don't understand what i'm saying
this place doesn't run without me i just
can't leave not even for a while
is there a problem here
and she who is she this is ranger anna
she's one of the officers in the task
force anyway like i said this is a very
important mission so
what are you waiting for let's go
i see but i have a duty to protect this
place
i'll fulfill my duty here for the sign
time
sammy
i understand your sense of
responsibility but i get it what
well
it's a dangerous mission no wonder he's
afraid
i understand
hey wait what did you just say
commander i don't think a scared ranger
should take part on the task force
excuse me
who are you calling a coward
you'll see a coward i'll show you who
the coward is
that's
some big trouble
max you are assigned to the task force
and must report back to headquarters
right now
what who me
ranger lucy the enemy took elenium
if we don't recover it soon they'll turn
it into a terrible weapon
you are assigned to the task force and
must report back to headquarters with us
you