You're not gonna believe this, but my robot dog is finally alive.
Wave to the audience, would you?
Oh my gosh dude, sit down.
Aw, I told you guys, the top comment would name it.
Whatever you want it.
With over 14,000 likes, you guys picked foam, F-O-A-M.
Now, the only question I have for you guys now,
because I did, in fact, name him foam.
What do you think foam should stand for?
And I wanted to see what he was actually capable of.
So I took him in my living room, I pet him, and then yeah, I kicked him.
Okay, but it was for science.
Then I pushed him, but don't worry, he's fine.
He might even like it weirdly.
He's way tougher than it looks, but he's probably plotting revenge.
Now, I introduced foam to my actual dog, and that was a mistake.
Apparently, my dog thinks foam is a threat to national security.
I think my dog hates him, but honestly, I kind of give it.
And then foam tried to assert dominance by jumping at her.
He can do so many different things like even climb,
but I haven't even tried that yet.
Let me know what else in the comments you want to see me do.