Hello, my name is Amori Dufreno. I am 19 years old student at the University of Technology of
Trian France currently in my second year of the Common Coal Programme. I have always been
passionate about technology and my goal is to specialize in cyber security, particularly in
ethical hacking and penetration testing. My interest in surveying as it seems is driven by the China
remarkable innovation and rapid technological advancement. I am particularly fascinated by the
dynamic ecosystem of research and development in the country. I believe that this opportunity
will broaden my global perspective and help me build a strong foundation for my career in cyber
security. If accepted, I plan to focus on improving both my technical expertise and cultural
understanding through cross-world research and collaboration with fellow students. Thank you
for considering my application. I look forward to contributing to and learning from this unique
academic environment. I look forward to contributing to and learning from this unique academic environment.