baby bus
hi i'm kiki
choose a tool and let's go fishing
swordfish
octopus
wow look at that
[Music]
puffer fish
kiki is wearing a wetsuit
[Music]
swordfish
it sounds amazing
[Music]
you did an amazing job
let's go fishing
[Music]
cart
lobster
it's jumping
[Music]
lobster
kissing gourami
it's so much fun
[Music]
the aquarium is frozen
help touch the screen
harp
you are so fast
[Music]
it is a tortoise shell
goldfish
it's super cute
[Music]
i'm so happy
kissing gourami it's so much fun
million fish
[Music]
harps
you are so fast
that was really awesome
[Music]
hi
i'm yumil
[Music]
japanese sea bream
fish
jellyfish
[Music]
look at those fishes
no a shark
[Music]
cuttlefish
[Applause]