I hate to give this satisfaction, asking how you're doing now, how's the castle built of people you pretend to care about, just what you want and
Look at you, cool guy, you got it, I see the parties and diamonds sometimes when I close my eyes, six months of torturing soul, there's some forbidden paradise, I'll love you truly
You got a laugh at the stupidity, cause I've made some real big mistakes, but you make the worst one look fine, I should have known it was strange
You only come out at night, I used to think I was smart, but you made me look so naive the way you saw me for parts, you suck your teeth into me
You're a blood sucker, fame fucker, bleedin' knee dry like a goddamn vampire
And every girl I ever talked to told me you were bad bad news, you called them crazy, God I hate the way I called them crazy too, you're so convincing
I deloid without flinching, I know what I'm mesmerizing, paralyzing fucked up lips, real can't figure out just how you do it and God knows I never will, and for me and I hurt
Cause girls, your age no better, I've made some real big mistakes, but you make the worst one look fine, I should have known it was strange
You only come out at night, I used to think I was smart, but you made me look so naive the way you saw me for parts, you suck your teeth into me
You're a blood sucker, fame fucker, bleedin' knee dry like a goddamn vampire
You said it was true love, but would not be hard, you can't love anyone, cause thought with me you had a heart, I tried to help you out, now I know that I can't, cause how you think is the kind of thing I'll never understand
I hate the way I called them crazy, God I hate the way I called them crazy, God I hate the way you saw me for parts, you suck your teeth into me
You're a blood sucker, fame fucker, bleedin' knee dry like a goddamn vampire